oil-testimonials.com 2012-10-17

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Oil-Testimonials.com uses and protects any information that you give Oil-Testimonials.com when you use this website.

Oil-Testimonials.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Oil-Testimonials.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from March 1, 2011.

###### What we may collect

  * Name 
  * Basic contact information, including email address and phone number 
  * Demographic information such as city location, preferences, and interests 
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers 

###### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

###### Internal record keeping

We may use the information to improve our products and services. We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers, or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email or phone. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

###### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

###### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites, and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

###### Controlling your personal information

We will not sell, distribute, or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. If you have previously agreed to allow us to use your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by notifying Member Services.
